optiontime.com 2014-07-06

# OptionTime – Privacy Policy Statement – Binary Options Trading

Protection of our users’ privacy and the safeguarding of our users’ personal and financial information is our upmost priority. This privacy policy outlines how Safecap Investments Limited (from hereon referred to as “Safecap” or “the Company”) collects, processes, stores and protects information collected from our users. By opening an account, a user hereby grants Safecap its consent to the collection, processing, storage and use of personal information by Safecap as explained below.

## Collection of personal information from binary option traders

Safecap collects information needed to open user accounts, carry out transactions, safeguard your privacy and assets, and provide users with the services they require. For these purposes, the Company gathers information from users and, in certain circumstances, may collect information from relevant banks, credit agencies, and/or other sources to assist us in profiling user requirements and preferences and in turn provide users with better services.

Information collected by Safecap may include:

**1\. Information from Applications**  
Personal information users provide us in their application forms, such as names, addresses, dates of birth, email addresses, income and income sources etc. in order to facilitate the evaluation of applications. The information provided to us is also used for communication purposes.

**2\. Information from Transactions**  
Information about the anticipated volume, and value, of users’ transactions with us, as well as income information provided in order to enable the creation of users’ economic profiles.

**3\. Information used for Verification**  
Information needed to verify client identity (for example, information from identification cards, passports or driver’s licenses). This may also include background information received about users through other entities not affiliated with Safecap Investments or through public records.

## How we use your personal information and your options

The personal information collected by the Company is used only as needed to provide quality service and security to our users. This information helps the Company in improving services, customizing browsing experiences and enabling us to inform users of additional services, products or promotions relevant to individual users and the products and services users’ require. Users hereby consent to Safecap using this information for such purposes.

If for any reason, you do not wish to receive information of this nature, please contact us at the following address: unsubscribe@optiontime.com. Please be aware that while you are not required to provide the Company any of the personal information that we may request, failure to do so may result in the Company being unable to open your account or provide you with the service(s) you require. Although we endeavor to make sure that all the information we maintain about you is accurate, complete, and current, we urge you to contact us without delay if any of your personal information has changed. 

## Protection of binary traders’ personal information 

The personal information provided to us by users will be treated as confidential and shared only within Safecap and its affiliates. The information will not be disclosed to any third parties except under regulatory or legal proceedings. The personal information provided to us by clients in connection with registering as a user of the site is safeguarded in many ways. Users can access their Registration Information through an individualized password selected by them. Passwords are encrypted and known only to users and shall not be revealed to anyone else. Registration Information is stored on secure servers and only accessible by authorized personnel.

The Company takes all possible precautions to prevent unauthorized parties from access to users’ personal information, including encrypting all personal information as transferred to the Company.

## The sharing of information with affiliates and partners

Under certain circumstances, the Company may share information with our trusted partners, affiliates and alliances if such information is reasonably required by those parties in order to offer other products and services of a similar nature that meet users’ requirements and which are delivered in a manner that is useful and appropriate to our users. Such sharing of information will take place only where users have authorized the Company to do so and/or to service client accounts.

## The sharing of information with non-affiliated third parties

Except as described in this Privacy Statement, Safecap does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose personal information of users to third parties. Safecap reserves the right to release information as necessary to credit reporting or collection agencies as reasonably required in order to provide the services to you. To help us improve our services, Safecap may appoint third parties to assist us in carrying out certain internal tasks such as account processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or other data gathering activities pertinent to our business. Shared information may also be utilized to impart legal, professional, or accounting advice to the Company. Except for the performance of the above, usage of shared information is strictly restricted and is not allowed for any other purpose. Third parties with whom Safecap shares personal data are obligated to protect such personal data in accordance with all applicable legislation and in a manner similar Safecap. Safecap will not disclose users’ personal data with third parties that it believes will not offer its users the upmost essential level of security. In cases whereby a Business Introducer has introduced a client to Safecap, such Business Introducer may have access to the client’s personal information. You hereby unequivocally and unambiguously consent to the sharing of information with such Business Introducer. You acknowledge that it may be necessary to transfer your information outside of the European Economic Area in order to provide services to you, and you consent to such transfer.

## Regulatory Disclosure Statement

The Company reserves the right to reveal personal information to third parties where required by law or by regulatory, law enforcement or other government authority of a competent jurisdiction in order to fully comply with legal proceedings and/or in order to protect the company’s rights. Unless otherwise directed by a regulatory or other government authority, such disclosure shall take place on a ‘need-to-know’ basis. Under such circumstances, Safecap shall explicitly notify the third parties about the confidential nature of the information.

## Restriction of the Company’s responsibility

Safecap is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of sites OptionTime links to and has no control of the use or protection of information collected by those sites or provided by Client. Client may be asked to provide registration or other information whenever Client elects to link to a co-branded website or to a linked website, Please note that such information is recorded by a third party and will be governed by the third party’s privacy policy.

## Use of “cookies “to optimize binary trading performance

Safecap utilizes cookies to improve the performance of the OptionTime.com website and secure users’ trading activities. Cookies utilizes by Safecap do not contain personal information or other sensitive data. Safecap may share website usage statistics with its affiliated marketing companies and advertising companies of good reputation. The data collected by advertising companies is not personally identifiable. To manage and enhance the OptionTime.com website, Safecap may utilize third parties to track and analyze statistical volume information and usage. Third parties may utilize cookies to track behavior and may set cookies on behalf of Safecap. These cookies also do not contain any personally identifiable information.

## Updates to our privacy statement

Safecap may modify or update parts of this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in applicable law and regulation or its practices. The Company invites users to monitor this Privacy Statement regularly in order to stay informed of any updates or changes to the Privacy Statement. In the event Safecap materially changes this Privacy Policy Statement, including how we collect, process or use your personal data, the revised Privacy Policy Statement will be posted on the website. Client agrees to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy Statement electronically on the website as actual notice to Client. Any dispute over our Privacy Policy Statement is subject to this notice and our Customer Agreement. Safecap encourages Client to regularly check back and review this privacy policy in order for Client to remain up to date on what information Safecap collects, how Safecap uses it, and to whom Safecap may disclose it.

## Agreement

I have read, understood and agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement, and I confirm that I have full power and authority to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. Please feel free to contact us with any further questions or concerns.
